STANDARD FOR LIFE
What you are about to watch is a perfect demonstration of the same kind of miracle
that happened in the life of the man at the Beautiful Gate in Acts 3.
Watch and see for yourself and give God the glory!
The Man At The Beautiful Gate | Crippled Man Walks Instantly | TB Joshua
Oh, look!
What a pitiful sight!
And what a sad story he must have of his suffering,
due to the debilitating condition he is in!
This poor handicapped man uses his hands and feet
to drag himself along the ground,
unable to afford a wheelchair or any alternative to get around.
This man has been in this crippled state for the past ten years.
With tears of despair running down his cheeks,
his face is an expression of utter helplessness.
He cries because he is not only lame, but living in abject poverty.
What poverty this is!
Can you imagine what it would be like to crawl on your hands and feet
as your only option to get from place to place.
My name is Ajayi Ogunleye.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN is that I am crippled; I cannot walk.
I don't have a helper unless God sends someone to bless me.
While sitting outside begging, I call any youth passing by to help me fetch water to bathe.
Sometimes, when I give people money and a plate to buy food for me,
they run away with it.
I am tired of all this; that is why I left there to come here.
I know that coming here, I will be healed.
Going home without healing, it would be better I die.
In search of even the basic necessities, he is here to meet Prophet T.B. Joshua
to care for his needs in terms of money, food, shelter, clothing,
or a wheelchair to aid his mobility.
Just as Prophet T.B. Joshua has been providing for others in the same situation as him.
He is seeking silver and gold.
But what is his essential need?
Is it silver and gold, or is it healing?
Look at his hands - calloused, rough and filthy
are the hands he uses to pull himself along the ground.
He reaches inside his ragged shirt
and brings out a soiled grobby sack which is tied around his neck.
From within the sack, he brings out a plastic bag containing all the money he has,
not even enough for a square meal.
Leaning to one side,
he shows the taterred foam padding he uses as a cushion
to make his moving a little less painful as he drags himself along.
The rough foam is all he has to protect himself from the hard earth, stones,
broken glass, nails, and other sharp objects he encounters all the time on his way.
He goes to wait for Prophet T.B. Joshua at the gate of The SCOAN
to ask for money and help just like the man at the Beautiful Gate in Acts 3
who asked for silver and gold.
But Apostle Peter, through the power of the Holy Spirit, gave him something
more than silver and gold - something that makes money insufficient.
He was given his essential needs.
Just exactly like the man at the Beautiful Gate,
this man sat at the gate of The SCOAN.
What could be his essential needs?
A wheel chair?
A house?
A meal?
A friend?
Is it money?
Or something more?
We pray his case would be like that of the man at the Beautiful Gate
who asked for money but instead received something more.
While Prophet T.B. Joshua was conducting the Sunday service, led by the Holy Spirit,
he moves outside the auditorium and walks through the street,
greeting members and receiving prayer requests.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, is on his way to the gate.
He sights the man and heads straight for him,
not even stopping to ask what he was doing there or why he had come,
as if he was looking for someone in need of healing.
God can use any medium to heal.
In this case, He uses Prophet T.B. Joshua's shoe as a point of contact.
In the name of Jesus, rise up!
The man awkwardly rises to his feet for the first time in ten years.
Before he even takes his first step,
Prophet T.B. Joshua leaves, knowing that it has been done.
As he often says, "I am not the Healer, I know the Healer, His name is Jesus Christ",
Jesus has healed this man.
It is a miracle.
Members who saw what had happened came forward
and gathered around the man at the gate,
encouraging him to move his legs one after the other.
Not used to standing on his legs, he is understandably somewhat unstable.
With each wobbly step, his confidence grows that he is healed indeed.
That week, the man went to show his family a great thing God had done in his life.
Overjoyed, his family followed him to The SCOAN
to appreciate God's goodness, testifying to the glory of God.
Mr. Ajayi now beautifully dressed in white trousers with a shirt and tie,
proudly rises to his feet and walks in front of his family, demonstrating his healing.
Before and After
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ajayi Ogunleye from Ondo State, Nigeria.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was that I was crippled.
I had been crippled for ten years.
Formerly, I was a herbalist. I tried to treat myself
and went to other herbalist friends but there was no way.
When I started begging to eat, I met a lady who introduced me to The SCOAN.
That was when I met Prophet T.B. Joshua, a picture of Jesus, in my dreams.
What I saw physically was that he put his foot on my legs and told me to stand up.
I stood up immediately. Since that time, I started to walk
and do everything by myself again. Today, I came from Akure by myself.
Therefore, I want the children of God to help me shout three times "Emmanuel".
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
The man of God did not collect any money from me.
My promise to God is to run from sin, to live the rest of my life for Jesus
and serve Him properly.
After sharing his heartwarming testimony,
Mr Ajayi stands up smartly and walks around the church auditorium.
Before and After
When Jesus says yes, no one can say no.
He is a mighty God.
Sharing his joy with the congregation and exchanging a few handshakes,
one can hardly believe that this gentleman was the same person
who crawled through the streets on his hands and feet.
When Jesus says yes, no one can say no.
When Jesus says it's Ok, no one can say no.
When Jesus says it's alright, no one can say no.
When Jesus says bless you, no one can say curse you.
Before and After
The evidence of Jesus Christ is lives changed.
Rejoicing with pilgrims to The SCOAN from all across the wold,
Mr Ajayi leads them in a processional dance.
Thank You, Jesus, for the man at the Beautiful Gate of our time.
RV: Mel Flowers 01/07/2018